Himanku Gogoi

Full Stack Web Developer



★ himankugogoi5@gmail.com

+919101087403

• Golaghat, Assam

in himankugogoi

nimanku

▶ Portfolio

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

An easy-going technology enthusiast and a strong communicator with a keen interest in solving problems. Good understanding of Data structures and Algorithms and hands-on experience working on various individual and collaborative software projects. Eagerly looking forward to utilizing and expanding my current skill set through challenging projects and proving my value and talent in a tech-based company.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Data Structures & Algorithms | HTML5

CSS3 | JavaScript | TypeScript

Next.js | React.js | Redux

Express.js | Node.js | MongoDB

MySQL | Cypress

SOFT SKILLS

Problem-solving | Adaptability

Attention to detail

INTERESTS

Bartending, Music, Learning Languages

LANGUAGES

English | Hindi | Assamese

Nagamese

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development (Full Time)

Masai School (Remote)

May 2022 - Present | Bengaluru, India

B. Tech in Electronics & Communication Engineering

National Institute of Technology Silchar

Jun 2017 - May 2021 | Silchar, India

PROJECTS

FitFreak.com 🛮 Github 🗗

It is a website where the users can locate its gyms, buy various fitness equipment and accessories, and connect to its community online.

Tech Stack: React.js | Chakra UI | AOS Animations | REST API **Features:**

- Aesthetic homepage UI with animations
- User authentication
- Developed the store section & the product preview page
- Add to cart functionality
- Responsive web design

An individual project developed within 4 days

Cricket.com Clone 2 Github 2

A holistic cricket app with every type of cricket data, starting from live score tracking to news, opinions, and insights from around the world of cricket

Tech Stack: HTML | CSS | JavaScript

Features:

- Signup and login
- Get ongoing live match scores
- Search players and find related information
- Responsive web design

Areas of responsibility:

- Implemented signup and login functionality with modal
- Developed the player page & the teams page
- Implemented player search & team search functionality.
- Maintained a responsive web design throughout

A collaborative project developed within 5 days, with a team of 3 members.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Guest Service Associate in Food & Beverage, Accor

Feb 2022 - May 2022 | Bengaluru

- Handled a range of duties and responsibilities around food and beverage management while maintaining professional hygiene and meeting organizational standards.
- Provided food and beverage recommendations, bartending service, in-room dining services, performed cashiering, handled point of sale systems, filled logreports, and managed beverage inventory.

Freelance Bartender

Nov 2021 - Jan 2022 | Goa

• Provided bartending service in various events, handled crowd smoothly while maintaining professionalism.